It will shorten the war by five years
and save millions of lives.
[CHATTERING AND CHEERING
ON TV]
(Raj:)Pause it. That's it. Confirmed.
(Raj:)We now have the address
of the Top Model house.
(Howard:)God bless you,
Google Street View registered trademark.
(Leonard:)Okay, for the record,
what you are doing is really creepy.
If it's "creepy" to use the Internet,
military satellites and robot aircraft...
(Howard:)...to find a house
full of gorgeous young models...
(Howard:)...so that I can drop in on them
unexpectedly, then fine, I'm "creepy."
[TELEPHONE RINGING]
Hello?
(Leonard(into phone, which has just rung):)Oh, hi.
Yeah, hold on a second, I'll get him.
(Leonard(into phone, which has just rung):)Sheldon, it's for you.
- Who is it?
- Your mother.
(Penny:)Oh, good.
(Sheldon:)Hi, Mom. How are you?
(Sheldon:)But, Mom.
(Sheldon:)She keeps sitting in my spot.